<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kiev Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_sightseeings">Sightseeings</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="button_voice">Speak</string>
    <string name="hotel_ukraine_description">The hotel was built in 1961 as
        the Hotel Moscow in a location which originally was occupied
        by Kiev`s first skyscraper, the Ginzburg House.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_hilton_description">
        The Hilton Kyiv hotel boasts a convenient location within
        walking distance of many major Kiev attractions such as
        Shevchenko Boulevard and the Old Botanical Gardens.
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_hyatt_regency_description">
        Located in the heart of the political and business capital of Ukraine
    </string>
    <string name="hotel_premier_palace_description">
        Premier Palace Hotel is a hotel in the centre of Kyiv.
        It is only 100 meters from Khreshchatyk – the main street of the capital.
    </string>
    <string name="park_taras_shevchenko_park_description">
        One of Kiev`s oldest parks is Shevchenko Park,
        which is located near the Priemer Palace Hotel.
        Opposite the park is the main building of the Taras Shevchenko University.
    </string>
    <string name="park_park_of_eternal_glory">
        The Park of Eternal Glory is a park in Kiev, Ukraine.
        It is located between Lavrska Street and the Dnieper Descent,
        and is surrounded by the Old Kiev-Pecherska fortress, and the Glory Square.
    </string>
    <string name="park_park_kioto_description">
        This park was founded to establish
        friendship between the capital of Ukraine
        Kiev and the capital of Japan Kioto in 1972
    </string>
    <string name="park_feofaniya_park_description">
        Feofaniya is a park located in the historical neighborhood on a tract
        near the southern outskirts of Kiev, the capital of Ukraine.
        The neighborhood is located in the administrative Holosiivskyi Raion
        amidst the neighborhoods of Holosiiv, Teremky, Pyrohiv and Khotiv.
        The park`s total area is about 1.5 km squared.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_meatbusters_description">
        In the menu of MEATBUSTERS are (spare ribs) pork and beef ribs of BBQ,
        beef brisket, turkey and also smoked sausages, sandwich of pulled pork.
        If you ever thought you couldn`t find American BBQ in Kyiv,
        think again! MeatBusters is the nearest to genuine BBQ I`ve had,
        even by US standards
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_shoti_restaurant">
        Shoti is a Georgian haute-cuisine restaurant.
        How could khachapuri, khinkali or lobio be haute-cuisine you
        may ask. Same as Robuchon`s mashed potatoes or Patterson`s
        beetroot "rose". Haute-cusine doesn`t need to consist of extravagant
        ingredients.
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_bao_description">
        Also known as steamed buns or baozi (包子),
        bao is a complete meal conveniently packed away
        in a white, warm, soft bun.
    </string>
    <string name="restaurant_beef_description">
        A premium restaurant in the very heart of Kiev.
        A combination of meat and wine is a main specialization
        of the restaurant. Its menu generously offers American
        and European cuisines. The restaurant serves beef, pork,
        lamb, ostrich and duck among the wide selection of meat.
    </string>

    <string name="sightseeing_kiev_pechersk_lavra_description">
        Kiev Pechersk Lavra, also known as the Kiev Monastery of the Caves,
        is a historic Orthodox Christian monastery which gave its name to one
        of the city districts where it is located in Kiev
    </string>
    <string name="sightseeing_the_motherland_monument_description">
        The Motherland Monument is a monumental statue in Kiev,
        the capital of Ukraine. The sculpture is a part of the National
        Museum of the History of Ukraine in the Second World War.
    </string>
    <string name="sightseeing_golden_gate_description">
        The Golden Gate of Kyiv was the main gate in the 11th century
        fortifications of Kyiv, the capital of Kievan Rus`.
        It was named in imitation of the Golden Gate of Constantinople.
        The structure was dismantled in the Middle Ages, leaving few vestiges
        of its existence.
    </string>
    <string name="sightseeing_gorodetsky_house_description">
        House with Chimaeras or Horodecki House is an Art Nouveau building
        located in the historic Lypky neighborhood of Kiev,
        the capital of Ukraine.
    </string>
</resources>
